<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android Studio Project</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="animators">
        <item>Slide left</item>
        <item>Slide right</item>
        <item>Slide top</item>
        <item>Slide bottom</item>
        <item>Scale</item>
        <item>Slide right and Scale</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="noboringactionbar_title">Beautiful picture</string>

    <string name="pulldown_scrollview">PulldownScrollView</string>
    <string name="stretch_scrollview">StretchScrollView</string>
    <string name="add_attention">加关注</string>
    <string name="user_post">职位：产品经理</string>
    <string name="user_book">书单：25本</string>
    <string name="user_name">西北老狼michael</string>
    <string name="user_des">谁能像优乐美一样把我捧在手心，我就能让他的儿子长的更帅女儿长的更漂亮</string>
    <string name="user_recommend_tip">TA推荐的好书</string>

    <string name="notify_priority">notify_priority</string>
     <string name="xiaomi_attention">
        <![CDATA[小米系统用户请进入系统应用:安全中心->授权管理->自启动应用管理 后允许『贝壳单词』自启动，否则无法自启动]]></string>
    <string name="toast_close">当前为关闭。\n开启后会在你使用其他 APP
        的时，定时弹出可爱的小『吐司』，不会妨碍你的触摸和点击事件，打扰性非常低，但却能很高效地无压力复习单词。
    </string>
    <string name="toast_open">当前为开启。\n开启后会在你使用其他 APP
        的时，定时弹出可爱的小『吐司』，不会妨碍你的触摸和点击事件，打扰性非常低，但却能很高效地无压力复习单词。
    </string>

    <string name="tower_of_london">The Tower of London has played a prominent role in English history. It was besieged several times and controlling it has been important to controlling the country. The Tower has served variously as an armoury, a treasury, a menagerie, the home of the Royal Mint, a public records office, and the home of the Crown Jewels of the United Kingdom. From the early 14th century until the reign of Charles II, a procession would be led from the Tower to Westminster Abbey on the coronation of a monarch. In the absence of the monarch, the Constable of the Tower is in charge of the castle. This was a powerful and trusted position in the medieval period. In the late 15th century the castle was the prison of the Princes in the Tower. Under the Tudors, the Tower became used less as a royal residence, and despite attempts to refortify and repair the castle its defences lagged behind developments to deal with artillery.</string>
</resources>
